<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Futbol Sites]]></title><description><![CDATA[Futbol Sites 04.2022]]></description><link>https://www.futbolsites.net/blog</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 19:20:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.futbolsites.net/pt/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Terms of use]]></title><description><![CDATA[The following are the legally binding terms &#38; conditions (collectively with the Privacy Policy), between each user and Futbol Sites, and...]]></description><link>https://www.futbolsites.net/post/terms-of-use</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6244ce1ed2470e4c21c35793</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 21:39:42 GMT</pubDate><dc:creator></dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><br /></p>
<p>The following are the legally binding terms &amp; conditions (collectively with the Privacy Policy), between each user and Futbol Sites, and govern the use of www.futbolsites.net and the content, features, services, websites, social media channels and applications offered by Futbol Sites. If you do not agree to any of these terms and conditions, please do not use the Service.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Proprietary Rights</p>
<p>All materials that are included in, made available on or are otherwise a part of the Service, including without limitation any and all articles, blogs, text, photos, images, illustrations, videos, application software, technologies, source and object codes, designs, graphics, layouts, artwork, logos and trademarks are owned or licensed by Futbol Sites or its affiliates or subsidiaries. Futbol Sites content is protected by copyrights, trademarks, service marks, patents and/or other proprietary rights and laws.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Content Disclaimers</p>
<p>Futbol Sites Content is provided for general informational purposes only. We make no representations, warranties or guarantees, whether express or implied, that the content on our Service is accurate, complete or up-to-date. No assurance is given that the information contained on the Services will always include the most recent findings or developments with respect to the particular material. We do not recommend or endorse any specific products, services, opinions, or other information that may appear on the Service.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>By using the Service, you may be exposed to content from other users, as well as material posted, uploaded, made available, shared or transmitted to or through the Service by us, that you may find offensive or otherwise objectionable. The views expressed by other users on our Service do not represent our views or values. Under no circumstances will we be liable or responsible in any way to any third party, for the content or accuracy of any content posted by you or any other user of our Service.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>User Content License Grant to Futbol Sites</p>
<p>By submitting or posting your User Content to or on the Service, you grant us, and our affiliates, agents, third party partners, and assignees a worldwide, non-exclusive, sublicensable, transferable, assignable, royalty-free and irrevocable license in perpetuity to host, display, transmit, distribute, publicly perform, reproduce, modify, edit, translate, copy, create derivative works from, store, sell, promote, sublicense and otherwise use your User Content in any and all manner and media, whether now known or hereafter devised, for any purpose whatsoever, commercial or otherwise. You also release all moral rights and similar rights in and to your User Content. You further perpetually and irrevocably grant Futbol Sites the unconditional right to use and exploit your name, person and likeness included in any User Content and in connection with any User Content, without any obligation, remuneration or attribution of any kind. You waive all rights and release Futbol Sites from any claim for defamation, invasion of right to privacy, infringement of rights of publicity or any similar matter, based upon or relating to the use of any User Content. You represent and warrant that any person or entity named or pictured in such User Content has provided any necessary licenses, rights, waivers or authorizations to allow Futbol Sites&apos;s use of such User Content in accordance with such license.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Sponsored Content</p>
<p>We may receive free products from marketers that we sometimes review or discuss in our editorial content. We may also run advertisements on our sites concerning some of those products or companies that sell them (and other products sold by such companies) for which we sometimes receive compensation.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Special Promotion Terms</p>
<p>Occasionally, we may offer the chance to participate in sweepstakes, contests, surveys and/or special offerings through the Service. Special Promotions may be governed by terms and conditions that are separate from these Terms of Use. It is your responsibility to read those Special Promotion terms and conditions to determine the sponsor&apos;s requirements of you in connection with the applicable Special Promotion. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Links To The Service</p>
<p>You may link to our website, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it. You must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval or endorsement on our part where none exists. You must not establish a link to our Service in any website that is not owned by you. Our Service must not be framed on any other Service.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>We reserve the right to revoke any link to any page of the Service or our social media channels in our sole discretion without notice. We also reserve the right to require that you obtain our prior written consent before you provide any links to any page or social media page of the Service.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Third Party Links</p>
<p>We may provide, or third parties may provide, on or through the Service, links to third party sites, such as other websites or resources. These third party sites are operated by parties who are separate from Futbol Sites. We have no control over such third party sites, we are not responsible for the availability of such third party sites and we do not endorse such third party sites. We are not responsible for or liable for any losses, expenses or damages, to you or your software, hardware or data, arising out of the operations of such third party sites.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Service Modification, Suspension Or Termination</p>
<p>We do not guarantee that our Service, or any content on it, will always be available or be uninterrupted. Access to our Service is permitted on a temporary basis. We reserve the right at any time and from time to time to withdraw, modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, all or any part of the Service with or without notice.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>We may at our sole discretion, under any circumstances, for any or no reason whatsoever and without prior notice to you, immediately terminate your access to the Service. We will not be liable or responsible to you or any third party for such termination. We also reserve the right to investigate suspected violations of these Terms of Use. Any violation of these Terms of Use may be referred to law enforcement authorities.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Indemnification</p>
<p>To the extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Futbol Sites, its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors, suppliers, partners and affiliates from and against all losses, liabilities, expenses, damages, and costs, including reasonable attorneys&apos; fees, resulting from any violation of these Terms of Use or any activity related to use of the Service (including negligent or wrongful conduct) by you or any other person accessing the Service via your email account(s), social media account(s) or IP address. We reserve the right to take over the exclusive defense of any claim. This section will survive termination of your access to the Service.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Designated Agent For Copyright Infringement Claim</p>
<p>If you have a good faith belief that your copyright is being infringed by any content on the Service, please send a notice that includes information listed below (the “Notice of Claimed Infringement”) to our Designated Copyright Agent:</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Designated Copyright Agent:</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Legal Department</p>
<p>18851 NE 29th Ave, Suite 700 Miami, FL 33180</p>
<p>email: contacto@futbolsitesnetwork.com</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Jurisdictional Issues</p>
<p>Our Service is directed to people residing in Latin America. We do not represent that content and materials available on or through our Service is appropriate or available in other locations. Those who choose to access the sites or use the Services from other locations do so on their own initiative and at their own risk, and are responsible for compliance with local laws in the United States of America, if and to the extent applicable. We may limit the availability of our Service or any service or product described on our Service to any person or geographic area at any time.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Governing Law; Jurisdiction; Arbitration; Commencement of Actions</p>
<p>These Terms of Use and the relationship between you and Futbol Sites will be governed by the laws of the United States of America and the State of Florida.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Any dispute relating in any way to your use of the Service will be submitted to confidential arbitration in Miami, Florida, except that, to the extent you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate our intellectual property rights, we may seek injunctive or other appropriate relief in any state or Federal court in another state, and you consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts. Arbitration under these Terms of Use will be conducted under the rules then prevailing of JAMS. The arbitrator’s award will be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction. To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under these Terms of Use will be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to these Terms of Use, whether through class arbitration proceedings or otherwise.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Any claim or cause of action arising out of or related to use of the Service or these Terms of Use must be filed within one year after such claim or cause of action arose or be forever barred. Any claim by you that may arise in connection with these Terms of Use will be compensable by monetary damages and you will in no event be entitled to injunctive or other equitable relief. You also hereby expressly waive any right to resort to any form of class action.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Miscellaneous</p>
<p>These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and us and govern your use of the Service. These Terms of Use supersede and extinguishes any prior agreements, promises, assurances, warranties, representations and undertakings between you and us, whether written or oral with respect to the Service. You also may be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you use other services, affiliate services, or third-party services.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>These Terms of Use are fully assignable by us and will be binding upon and inure to the benefit of our successors and assigns. No agency, partnership, joint venture, employee-employer or franchiser-franchisee relationship is intended or created by these Terms of Use. Our failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Use will not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. If any provision of these Terms of Use is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the court should nevertheless endeavor to give effect to the parties’ intentions as reflected in the provision, and the other provisions of these Terms of Use will remain in full force and effect. The headings in these Terms of Use are for convenience only and have no legal or contractual effect.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>We shall not be liable for any failure to perform our obligations hereunder where such failure results from any cause beyond our reasonable control, including, without limitation, mechanical, electronic or communications failure or degradation.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Updates To These Terms</p>
<p>We reserve the right to change any terms of these Terms of Use at any time without prior notice to you. You agree that our posting of revised Terms of Use on our Service will constitute notice to you of such revised Terms of Use and that your access or use of the Service after such posting constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes and the revised Terms of Use. Consequently, please review these Terms of Use before each and any access or use of our Service. Any changes to these Terms of Use will become a part of these Terms of Use and will apply as soon as they are posted or such later date as may be specified in the posted Terms of Use.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Unless explicitly stated otherwise, any new features or functionality that augment or enhance the Service will be subject to these Terms of Use.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Soccerex press release]]></title><description><![CDATA[Miami – Futbol Sites, top digital sports media group in Latinamerica, announces a key Media Partnership with Soccerex, leading event...]]></description><link>https://www.futbolsites.net/post/soccerex-press-release</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6244ce1ed2470e4c21c35792</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 21:39:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/a323de_82b619d5072340dd80a9af0319d7c6de~mv2_d_5100_3456_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator></dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><br /></p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/a323de_82b619d5072340dd80a9af0319d7c6de~mv2_d_5100_3456_s_4_2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p>Miami – Futbol Sites, top digital sports media group in Latinamerica, announces a key Media Partnership with Soccerex, leading event provider for the global soccer industry.</p>
<p>Soccerex Global Convention will take place in Manchester, London from September</p>
<p>4th – 6th, 2017, where more than 3.000 delegates, 450 clubs, 220 media presses and 170 exhibitors will be attending. </p>
<p>“It is a pleasure to close this partnership with Soccerex, promoting their events and amplifying its generated content during the Global Convention, as well as, be an active partner creating content through Soccerex social media channels. This Media Partnership, will allow us to extent our global relationships within the soccer industry, prior the World Cup, most important worldwide event” said Federico Grinberg, CEO of Fultbol Sites. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<h1>Futbol Sites, is known as the most growing sport vertical in Latinamerica, with one of the largest audience in its category, reaching more than 25 million of unique users every month on its websites. It operates more than 80 fan pages on Facebook, with more than 30 million fans and 100 million users reached every month. </h1>
<h1></h1>
<p>Soccerex, has been recognized as the leading event provider for the global soccer industry. The Global Convention, gathers top buyers and suppliers to offer a unique commercial environment, where delegates will benefit from exclusive networking and business opportunities, for 3 days at one of the biggest soccer cities in the world.  </p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>